gameriot.com 2013-04-11

# Privacy - GIANT REALM

Giant Realm respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us on our web sites.  The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our site. Personal information includes your name, e-mail addresses, click-through activity and any other personal information you may provide here.  

## Ownership

Giant Realm is owned by Burst Media and uses the company’s ad serving technology to manage advertising that appears on the site.   Burst Media’s privacy policy can be viewed here <http://www.burstmedia.com/privacy.html>.    

##  Privacy

All users who receive an ad served by Giant Realm retain complete anonymity where Giant Realm is concerned. As ads are delivered, Giant Realm does not acquire or collect any personal information about you. Your name, address, phone number, and email address all remain your private property. Giant Realm does, however, collect information that is specific to how you use the Internet. This non-personally identifying information can include, and is not limited to, the server you are logged onto, the geographic location of the ISP you use, the type of browser you use, and your IP address. This information is obtained solely for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring a given ad's effectiveness on behalf of Giant Realm clients and customers.  
There are instances where a user may provide specific personal information in response to an ad containing a survey, purchase agreement, or registration questionnaire. For such programs, Giant Realm (or a third party working in conjunction with Giant Realm and the advertiser) acquires this information on behalf of the advertiser client. The client uses this information to deliver the goods or services requested by the user. When requested, Giant Realm may employ this information in a compiled format without identifying users specifically to provide to the advertiser client precise profiles of the types of individuals responding to the ads.  

##  Use of Giant Realm Cookies 

Giant Realm may use cookies to improve your Web browsing experience. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer for the purpose of identifying your web browser. When you are served a Giant Realm ad, Giant Realm may assign in a cookie various information on ads you've seen, information on sites you've visited and activities performed to your computer browser. We do this to understand the way a user responds to the ads we deliver. For example, this information lets us keep track of how many times you view an ad we distribute. Likewise, the cookie can help make sure you do not see the same ad over and over - thus enhancing your online Web viewing experience.  
Giant Realm Media collects this information via our technology and it may be stored for up to 2 years for the purpose of: 1) analyzing campaign results, 2) ensuring that our technology is functioning properly, and 3) preventing fraud across our sites.

We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site or our member sites. We may obtain anonymous information about you - such as sites you have visited or products you have researched - from third-party sources, and combine it with data that we have collected to better target advertising that match your interests. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that use if you desire.  

In an effort to respect your privacy, Giant Realm, through its association with Burst Media, gives all internet users the choice to opt-out of receiving Giant Realm cookies. If you would like to opt out, please visit Burst Media’s Cookie Opt-out Program at [www.burstmedia.com/optout.html](http://www.burstmedia.com/optout.html). Alternatively, you may also choose to opt out of receiving Giant Realm cookies through the Network Advertising Initiative's [Consumer Opt-Out Program](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).  

##  Other Disclosure of Personal Information 

Giant Realm will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, or (ii) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority. This policy does not protect information you post to any public forum within our Web site.  

## Other Sites

Giant Realm contains many links to other sites on the Web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other Web sites.  

## Third Parties

Often, advertisers will employ a third-party service provider other than Giant Realm for serving the advertisements and for tracking the performance of an ad program. These companies may employ cookie and 1x1 pixel technology to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their client. These companies may collect and use anonymous information about your visits to our member websites and other websites. The information collected can include:

  1. Date/time of your visit
  2. The banner ad that was shown
  3. Unique user ID
  4. Your IP address
  5. The URLs of sites you visit

This information can also be used for online preference marketing ("profiling") purposes. In these instances, Giant Realm has no control over the information collected by the third-party, and may not be held responsible for the actions of the third-party measurement service where collected information is concerned.  

##  Notifications of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Regardless of later updates, we will never use the information you submit under this current policy in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

Giant Realm c/o Burst Media  
8 New England Executive Park  
Burlington, MA 01803
